ADRIAN DAVID LLOYD

CONTACT

+1 (647)-550-0754

adrian-lloyd@outlook.com

http://www.adrianlloyd.xyz

1378 Seymour Street, Halifax, NS, CA B3H 3M5

Canada/UK Dual Citizen

SKILLS SNAPSHOT

- Java, C#, Dart, Python, HTML, and a wide variety of other languages
- Team leadership
- Collaboration and interpersonal relations
- · Organization and determination
- Innovation and collaboration

EDUCATION

Dalhousie University

Bachelor's of Computer Science

2021 - present

2023 DSU O-Week Leader

Phi Delta Theta Fraternity - Nova Scotia Alpha Chapter

- Chapter President 2022-2023
- Chapter Vice-President 2021-2022
- Attended the 2023 General Convention, the 2023 Mackenzie Presidents' Leadership Conference, and the 2022 Kleberg Emerging Leaders' Institute as a chapter delegate
- NSA Chapter Phi of the Year 2022, 2023

Georgetown District High School

OSSD (Honour Roll)

2017 - 2021

FRC Team 4976 - Revolt Robotics

- Programming sub-team co-lead 2019-2020
- Designed and implemented robot commands and subsystems in Java using WPII ih
- Developed an app to track and analyze opponents' performance in tournaments, and upload data to a Firebase server
- FIRST Dean's List team nominee

PROFILE

Adrian Lloyd is a Developer and Computer Science student with over a decade of programming experience, and a half-decade of organizational leadership experience. He has extensive experience in over a dozen programming languages, and is fluent in Java, C#, Dart, Python, Ruby, and HTML/CSS, among others, and a strong background in customer relations and customer service roles

Adrian is a decorated senior member of Phi Delta Theta, an international leadership fraternity, having traveled across the continent to delegate on behalf of his chapter.

He is entrepreneurial and hard-working, having run his own tutoring business since 2019 and has held multiple customer service positions. In his free time, Adrian enjoys writing, playing guitar and listening to music and is interested in Philosophy and Metaphysics. He also devotes time to side projects in game development and other software engineering endeavours and remains committed to honing his craft further every day.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Data Annotation Inc.

2024 - present

- Analyzes, qualifies, and verifies code produced in AI model outputs, reporting on its effectiveness and efficiency
- Engineers prompts to test and challenge LLMs
- Refines LLM responses by writing code in a variety of languages, including Java, Python, Rust, and HTML
- Develops custom solutions to programming problems to improve quality of training data

STEM Tutor

Adrian Lloyd Tutoring

2019 - present

- Offers personalized tutoring sessions to students of all ages, specializing in mathematics and computer science
- Maintains and organizes a detailed schedule of tutoring appointments
- Supports students with learning accommodations identified within their Individualized Education Plans

Data Analyst

Transperfect

2023

- Reported accurately and efficiently on the quality of search engine query results, relative to user satisfaction metrics
- Generated thorough reports and results to assist in training AI-powered SEO algorithms
- Worked independently to fulfill a 6 month analyst contract

Parks and Recreation Student

Town of Halton Hills

Summer 2022

- Performed thorough care and maintenance on municipal parks and cemeteries, including grass cutting and other landscaping
- Completed numerous individual tasks as requested, including waste management and disposal, event preparation and minor repairs
- Provided support to colleagues and worked collaboratively to improve effectiveness and efficiency

Crew Member

McDonald's Canada

2019-2021

- Created and maintained a positive customer service experience for guests
- Often worked overnight shifts and ensured store was stocked and organized for the next day
- Consistently collaborated with team members to improve timeliness of food delivery

ADRIAN DAVID LLOYD

+1 (647)-550-0754



adrian-lloyd@outlook.com



1378 Seymour Street, Halifax, NS, CA B3H 3M5



http://www.adrianlloyd.xyz

SOFT SKILLS

Proven Leadership

o Adrian has excelled within the Phi Delta Theta leadership fraternity and has garnered recognition and won awards at the local and international levels, for his exceptional leadership and commitment to diversity

· Intuition, Initiative and Innovation

o Adrian has excelled as a developer, and has a demonstrably strong interdisciplinary ability to learn new frameworks and tools rapidly, using them to build innovative solutions

Collaboration and Communication

 Through organizational management and leadership, and through collaborative team development projects, Adrian has developed exceptional writing, communication and collaboration skills.

· Attention to Detail

o As a developer, and as a Software Engineer with Data Annotation, Adrian has demonstrated a keen eye for detail, and a meticulous perfectionism which drives his development style.

. Unmatched Work Ethic

o Adrian's deep-seated passion and commitment to build and innovate in the fields of software engineering and computer science perfectly compliment his strong work ethic, which he first demonstrated in the food service and manual labour jobs he held throughout his adolescence.

· Entrepreneurial and Dedicated

 Having started and operated his own successful tutoring business for over 5 years, Adrian channels his dedication and passion for STEM fields into an entrepreneurial spirit, thriving when faced with challenges, and working best under pressure.

SKILLS INVENTORY

Languages (with releases/libraries/frameworks)

- Pvthon
 - Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, TensorFlow, and many more
- Visual Basic
 - VB.NET, VBA
- Java
 - AWT, Swing, JavaFX, JUnit 5, WPILib, Gradle and more
- HTML + CSS
- Javascript
- C
- C++
- C#
- Unity Engine, .NET
- Ruby
- Dart
 - Flutter (mobile + web)
- Swift
 - Foundation, SwiftUI, SwiftData and more

- Assembly
 - RISC-V, MIPS, x86 (AT&T, Intel)
- Go
- SQL
 - MySQL
- ActionScript
 - AS2, AS3

Development Tool Experience Snapshot

- Git VCS
 - o GitHub (with Actions), GitLab (using CI/CD)
- Xcode, JetBrains IDEs, Atom, VSCode, and many more
- Bash/Shell Scripting
- Firebase
 - o DataStore, etc.
- MySQLWorkbench
- Unity 5 & Unreal Engine 5
- Gradle
- Maven

Among many others

NOTABLE PROJECTS (WITH AWARDS)

- 2024 Global Game Jam Submission: Get Out VR
 - Dalhousie People's Choice Award -- Most Ambitious Game
- 2023 Global Game Jam Submission: Tree of Life
- 2021 Jame Gam 7 Submission: Floating Factories
 - Ranked fourth overall
- 2021 2-Buttons Jam Submission: SMASHSMASHSMASH
- 2019 FIRST™ Robotics Competition Team 4976 Scouting App
- 2018-2021 FIRST™ Robotics Competition Team 4976 Robot **Development**
 - 2020 FIRST™ Dean's List Nominee

References available upon request